哇
Whoa.
刚才的舞蹈太酷了  Q 舞帝
That was awesome, qpop.
对  我从来不会停下脚步
Yeah, q-pop don't stop.
噢
Oh.
J 舞者要驾到了哟
Mc j-town in da house.
J 舞者真有个性
Mc j-town be his own boy.
致敬
Respect!
乔伊  这是 Q 舞帝
Joey, this is q-pop.
他是我们的舞蹈教练
He's our dance instructor.
噢  那好  很高兴见到你  舞帝先生
Oh, well, it's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. pop.
我的使命就是跟随新潮  保持新潮  还要不断刷新潮流
My mission is to get fresh, stay fresh, then refresh.
这就是我的座右铭  托付给你们这犄角旮旯了
I just dropped my motto on this grotto.
这真是酷毙了
This is so cool.
我不敢相信玛蒂不在这儿
I can't believe Maddie bailed.
我简直无拘无束了
I feel so alive.
她失去的正是霹雳舞好哥们得到的
Her loss is the breaking bros' gain.
再说了  谁知道我住在这么一个犄角旮旯呢
Plus, who knew I lived in a grotto.
对吗
Right?
各就各位  让我来看看你们练得咋样了
All right. Let's see what y'all are working with.
来引领潮流吧  呀哈
Time to get fresh, y'all.
当我开始放节奏  我就要看你们跳机器人舞
When I drop the beat, I want to see you robot.
哦  不
Oh... no.
同志们  你们是故意要气哭我吗
Gentlemen, are y'all trying to make q-pop cry?
好了  我们现在退回到几个简单的动作  明白了吗
All right, let's try to back it up to a simpler move, okay?
这个动作叫“找准节奏”
This one is called "finding the beat!"
等一下  慢点来
Okay, wait. Slow down.
你们到底是怎么打响指的啊
How are you making that noise with your fingers?